Most of us compare ourselves with anyone we think is happier﻿
﻿ — a relative, someone we know a lot, or someone we hardly ﻿
﻿ know. As a result, what we do remember is anything that makes﻿
﻿  others happy, anything that makes ourselves unhappy, totally﻿
﻿   forgetting that there is something happy in our own life.So﻿
﻿ the best way to destroy happiness is to look at something and focus﻿
﻿  on even the smallest flaw. It is the smallest flaw that would make ﻿
﻿  us complain. And it is the complaint that leads to us becoming unhappy.﻿
﻿If one chooses to be happy, he will be blessed; if he chooses to be unhappy, ﻿
﻿he will be cursed. Happiness is just what you think will make you happy.﻿
